(Sheldon:)Oh, yeah. This is it.
Leonard. Leonard. Leonard.
(Leonard:)What, Sheldon? What, Sheldon?
What, Sheldon?
(Sheldon(showing him laptop):)Tell me what you see here.
(Leonard:)The blunt instrument
that will be the focus of my murder trial?
(Sheldon:)This is Stephanie's Facebook page.
(Sheldon:)Now, where it should say
"in a relationship," what does it say?
- "Stephanie Barnett is single."
- Yeah, furthermore...
(Sheldon:)...earlier this evening, she threw
a digital sheep at some guy named Mike.
(Sheldon:)Who's Mike? Why does he
get a digital sheep and not you?
(Leonard:)It's just her Facebook page, and we've
only been going out a couple of weeks.
(Sheldon:)You don't see it, do you?
We're losing her.
Okay, I'm gonna make this very simple
for you.